A while ago, I'm sorry.
ちょっと前はね、ごめんなさい
I'm reflecting on it.
反省してます
Also, I heard that it was hard because it got on my face.
あと は話聞いて、顔にかかっちゃって大変だったって
I heard that you were angry, and I feel very sorry for it.
怒っちゃったって聞いて、すごく反省してます
Today, as I said earlier,
今日は、さっきの話だったように、
It's nothing like before.
その前みたいなことないよ
Forgive me for remembering.
記 憶的とは、許してください
I'm sorry.
すみませんでした
sorry.
ごめんなさい
yes.
はい
Is this okay?
大丈夫、これ?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Please let me wash away what happened the other day.
この前のことは、ちょっと水に流してもらって
yes.
はい
I came to the hotel again today.
今日もホテル来たんでね
I want to do what I like.
好きやること、やりたいと思います
I'm nervous.
緊張してるって
Are you nervous?
緊張している?
Yeah.
うん
It's okay, I'll be more considerate today than before.
大丈夫、今日はこの前以上に配慮するんで、
rest assured.
安心してください
This is the basis of reconciliation.
これ、仲直りの基礎ね、これ
It's been a while since Yuki showed me her beautiful body.
久しぶりにゆきちゃんの、きれいな体を見せて
Hey, I need to stand up for a second.
ちょっと さ、ちょっと立っておらないと
It's simple.
シンプルだね
good?
いい?
Be considerate, Yuki-chan.
気立つように、ゆきちゃん
That's cute.
かわいいのが
Slow down, watch the clock.
ゆっくりさ、時計マーニングで
Hey, show me your butt.
ちょっと、お尻見せて
Hey, can you touch my butt like this?
ちょっとさ、お尻、こう、つきなせる?
Can you use your hands to make pants look like a tea bag?
手でさ、パンツさ、ティーバックみたいにできる?
Let me dig in.
食い込ませてさ
That's amazing, butt taken.
すごいな、お尻取られてる
Why do you fall off your feet?
何で足を落ちるの?
No, no.
いやいや
picture?
え?
Yuki-chan, she looks a little smug.
ゆきちゃん、ちょっとなんか、しみみっぽいのが
picture?
え?
what happened?
どうしたの?
It stands out a little because it's true pants.
ちょっと、トルーパンツだから目立つよ、
A stain.
しみが
Hey, let me see.
ちょっと、見せて
I have to keep my hands close.
手を近くにしておらないと
Take a deep breath.
深呼吸して
I felt hurt and turned into an ass.
傷を感じて、お尻になっちゃった
I wonder what happened.
どうしたんだろうね
Yuki-chan is flashy again, this time wearing Kismak.
ゆきちゃん、派手にまた、今回もキスマックつけて
amazing
すごい
hey.
ね
Can I take it too?
俺 も受けていい?
picture?
え?
As expected, chan.
やっぱりね、ちゃん
If you put it close to him, he won't know, right?
近いところにつけたら、彼は分かんないじゃない?
I don't know.
分かんない
I think it's better if I do it.
俺がやった方がいいと思うじゃん
picture?
え?
Do you want somewhere nearby?
近いところがいいの?
picture?
え?
What if it's thinner?
薄くなら?
If it's thin, I'll put on something amazing.
薄くなら、すごいのつけちゃう
There was a thin one on it.
薄いのついた
It's probably okay.
多分大丈夫
Then go somewhere nearby.
じゃあ、近いところに行ってこな
I feel tired and try to close my eyes.
くたくなり、なんか閉じようとする
Yeah, it's embarrassing.
うん、恥ずかしい
Karakang, you don't have to have that much leeway.
カラカン、そんなに余裕なくていいよ
There are quite a few stains.
だいぶシミが
Amazing, Yuki-chan, it's easy to sleep.
すごい、ゆきちゃん、寝やすい
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
what happened?
どうしたの?
I opened it with both hands.
両手で開いてみちゃった
Did you show me your camera?
カメラ見せた?
If you're told it won't open anymore,
もうこれじゃ開かないよって言われたら、
Open it.
開いて
picture?
え?
I don't know.
分かんない
It looks fine.
ちゃんとよく見えるよ
I can see the crazy kids too.
狂った子も見えるよ
It feels like my face is being peeled off.
顔剥いちゃうくらいの感じ
You can't hide it, Yukita.
隠しちゃダメだよ、ゆきて
I wish I could show it properly.
ちゃんと見せたらいいな、
After.
あと
I'll go in from there, no matter what.
そ っちから入っちゃうね、どうしても
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I can't get used to it.
慣れないね
This is what I've been using the other day.
これ、この前も使ってるんだ、これね
Yeah.
うん
Do you remember?
覚えてる?
This feeling.
この感触
Strange.
不思議な
I felt a bit twitchy.
ちょっと、ピクンってなった
I'll do it quickly.
早くしておくよ
Can you hear the sound?
音聞こえる?
It's okay to look at your strength
力見ちゃっていいんだ
Yo.
よ
You're talking about something bad.
何 か悪な話してるんだ
Okay, tell me to breathe.
いいよ、呼吸と伝えて
You can sprinkle it on your chest.
胸元にそれを散っていいよ
What if?
何 だったら
You can see the full amount.
全額見えてるよね
Okay, pretend you're Six.
いいよ、シクスなのになってごらん
Please change the total amount.
全額変えてごらん
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
It's okay to take a break, just do it.
休み休みでいいからやってごらん
I can't concentrate.
集中できない
Relax.
力抜くんだよ
I'll stay like this for a while.
ちょっとこのままでいるね
appear?
見える?
Do you understand?
分かってる?
Can you maintain the condition?
状態を保せる?
My hands, here, behind my back, where it doesn't work.
手とか、ここでも、後ろでもダメなところで
It can move up and down.
上下に動けたりする
I don't mind going out as long as I want.
ひ たすら出てもいいわ
You can take it slow.
ゆっくり、手ついていいよ
So slowly move up and down.
それで、ゆっくり上下に
Yeah, yeah, it's okay to take it slow.
そうそうそう、ゆっくりでいいよ
Good, good.
上手、上手
Oh, is that so?
あ、そっから?
Is it good that the ban on exposing your stomach has been lifted?
お腹出しは解禁で良かった?
It's okay if you say hello over there.
いいよ、そっからでこんにちはしてても
Wasn't it good?
良くなかった?
Anyway, I'm glad I was able to make a temporary recovery.
とりあえず、中治りできたから良かったわ
Thank you.
あり がとね
It was fun today too.
楽しかったね、今日も
Thank you.
ありがとね